Sae Pak

Front-end developer

[] (236) 986-2247

in linkedin.com/in/sae-pak

www.sae-pak.com

https://github.com/saepak

Profile

A detail-oriented front-end developer and self-motivated professional with extensive team collaboration involvement. Over three years experience building websites and web applications for a multitude of clients. Continually working on the improvement of technical skill levels through personal and team projects.

Technical Skills

SKILLS HTML5/CSS3/SASS/JavaScript/NPM/React/React Hooks/GraphQL/jQuery

TOOLS Visual Studio Code / Git / Android Studio / Xcode

OTHER UI framework / Trello / Slack / MS office

Project Experience

Kovan / Front-end Developer

May 2020 - Aug 2020

An all-in-one group management solution with 7 plug-ins.

- Collaborated with team members to plan and execute a native app.
- Built and implemented a to-do list and poll plug-in with React Native and React Hooks.
- Created graphs in poll plug-in with SVG for scalability and easy editing.
- Styled the app with Native-Base to reduce the built time.
- Made the promotional website using React.js. to show the seven different plug-ins and our marketing plans.

Personal Project Experience

Movie Box

A web app that lets you search for movies and TV shows.

- Created search and filter features using React.js.
- Fetched TMDB Movie API to provide massive data about movies and TV shows.
- Styled the components using Material-UI for responsive design.

My Expense Manager

A simple management app that enables users to track their expense.

- Built features to create and submit expenses for easy budgeting.
- Used Google OAuth to keep data safe and provide strong authentication.
- Created a chart to visualize expenses.

Pixabay Image Gallery

A high quality image library.

- Fetched Pixabay API for searching and retrieving free images.
- Created a search function to make it easy to find images.
- Used Tailwind CSS for faster styling process and cross browser.

Work Experience

Emeye (Seoul, South Korea) / UI developer

Dec 2015 - Dec 2017

- Built websites and web apps using HTML5, CSS3 and jQuery.
- Validated CSS style sheet using W3C Validation Service for error-free performances.
- Worked on websites maintenance including correcting issues and making updates to ensure that client's websites are running at full capacity.

Konest (Seoul, South Korea) / UI developer

Mar 2014 - May 2015

- Changed the website code from HTML3 to HTML5 / CSS3 and made it responsive.
- Collaborated with content managers and web designers to create web pages for the up-to-date information delivery.
- Updated the website to make it easier to use and navigate.
- Worked with clients to create customized landing pages for their marketing campaign.

Education

Langara college (Vancouver, Canada)

Post-Degree Diploma, Web and Mobile App Design and Development Developer stream / Dean's Honour Roll

Sungshin Women's University (Seoul, South Korea)

Bachelor's degree, Japanese Language and Literature.





